[
    {
        "question": "Zagreb is the capital of which European country?",
        "answer": "Croatia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Sudan to the north?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country does Egypt border to the south?",
        "answer": "Sudan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Sudan?",
        "answer": "Khartoum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Khartoum is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Sudan "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most common street name in the United States?",
        "answer": "Park, according to a Washington Post study"
    },
    {
        "question": "What continent is Morocco located in?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the Texan city of Austin named after?",
        "answer": "Stephen F. Austin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only country capital that contains a national park?",
        "answer": "Nairobi, Kenya"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2020, which US state had the most craft breweries?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the language with the world`s shortest alphabet?",
        "answer": "Papua New Guinea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What part of Russia is surrounded by Lithuania and Poland?",
        "answer": "Kaliningrad"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. city`s airport code is MCO?",
        "answer": "Orlando, Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s largest building carved out of a single rock?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Wolverine State`?",
        "answer": "Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Massachusetts?",
        "answer": "Boston"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Catskill Mountains are part of what larger mountain chain?",
        "answer": "Appalachian Mountains"
    },
    {
        "question": "The English explorer Admiral John Franklin discovered what in the 1840s?",
        "answer": "The Northwest Passage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Through which continent does the Crocodile River run?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state would you find the zip code 12345?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "The world`s northernmost capital is found in which Scandinavian country?",
        "answer": "Iceland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Australia?",
        "answer": "Canberra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Devil`s Island, once the world`s most notorious penal colony, is located off the coast of what country?",
        "answer": "French Guiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only walled city north of Mexico?",
        "answer": "Quebec City, Quebec, Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Atlantic Ocean Road links islands in what country?",
        "answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest city in Switzerland?",
        "answer": "Zurich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the first European town in the Americas built?",
        "answer": "Dominican Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only U.S. state with the Union Jack on its flag?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "N`Djamena is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Chad"
    },
    {
        "question": "N`Djamena is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Chad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Chad to the north?",
        "answer": "Libya"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Chad to the east?",
        "answer": "Sudan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bay does the Ganges River flow into?",
        "answer": "Bay of Bengal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?",
        "answer": "Abu Dhabi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phoenix is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Arizona"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mauritania is in which continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent is Mauritania a part of?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Acadia was the original name of which Canadian province?",
        "answer": "Nova Scotia "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Kuwait?",
        "answer": "Kuwait City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are the Sigatoka sand dunes located?",
        "answer": "Fiji"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country will you find most of the Aral sea in?",
        "answer": "Kazakhstan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Missouri?",
        "answer": "Jefferson City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which constellation appears on Australia`s flag?",
        "answer": "The Southern Cross"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Canadian province is immediately east of British Columbia?",
        "answer": "Alberta"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Province of Saskatchewan shares its southern border with which two US states?",
        "answer": "Montana and North Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of dancing is usually performed in conjunction with May Day celebrations in England?",
        "answer": "Morris dance"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color do people wear for the New Year in Brazil?",
        "answer": "White"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosts the World Ice Golf Championship?",
        "answer": "Greenland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is traditionally said to be built on seven hills?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two towns were destroyed and buried when Mount Vesuvius erupted in 79 A.D.?",
        "answer": "Pompeii and Herculaneum were both destroyed by the eruption in 79 A.D."
    }
]